Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Index: DE37-03. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - Community Relations., 1979-1997. (Box 488, Folder 5)
- Index: DE37-02. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - UCLA Environs., 1992-1996. (Box 489, Folder 1)
- Index: DE37-02. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - UCLA Environs., 1992-1996. (Box 489, Folder 1)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Includes: Buspool)., 1989-1996. (Box 489, Folder 2)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Includes Buspool)., 1989-1996. (Box 489, Folder 2)
- Index: DE37-02. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - UCLA Environs., 1990-1992. (Box 489, Folder 3)
- Index: DE37-02. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning -UCLA Environs., 1990-1992. (Box 489, Folder 3)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning., 1986-1992. (Box 489, Folder 4)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Includes: Tennis Court Lighting Comp., 1986-1992. (Box 489, Folder 4)
- Index: DE37-08. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - Commuter Assistance Ride Sharing., 1977-1992. (Box 489, Folder 5)
- Index: DE37-08. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - Commuter Assistance Ride Sharing., 1977-1992. (Box 489, Folder 5)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning., 1971-1989. (Box 490, Folder 1)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Includes: Proposition U; Traffic Abal., 1971-1989. (Box 490, Folder 1)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (UCLA Enivons Westwood Special Plan)., 1983-1987. (Box 490, Folder 2)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (UCLA Enivons Westwood Specific Plan)., 1983-1987. (Box 490, Folder 2)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (WCPC-UCLA Community Meeting)., 1981-1987. (Box 490, Folder 3)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (WCPC-UCLA Community Meeting)., 1981-1987. (Box 490, Folder 3)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning., 1983-1986. (Box 490, Folder 4)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Includes: Neighbors Booklet, Bus Shel., 1983-1986. (Box 490, Folder 4)
- Index: DE37-04. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - West LA Veloway., 1984-1986. (Box 490, Folder 5)
- Index: DE37-04. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - West LA Veloway., 1984-1986. (Box 490, Folder 5)
- Index: DE37-04. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning- West LA Veloway., 1975-1983. (Box 491, Folder 1)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Westwood Hills Property Owners)., 1978-1983. (Box 491, Folder 2)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning., 1978-1982. (Box 491, Folder 3)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Board of Directors West LA Veloway )., 1981. (Box 491, Folder 4)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (UCLA Enivons- Westwood Specific Plan)., 1978-1979. (Box 491, Folder 5)
- Index: DE37. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Planning Office - Campus Planning - (Include: Evening Campus Tran, ect)., 1970-1978. (Box 491, Folder 6)
- Index: E7/V4-04. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land - Parking Lots on VA Property., 1975-1992. (Box 492, Folder 1)
- Index: E7/V4-02. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land - VA Research Building., 1988-1992. (Box 492, Folder 2)
- Index: E7/V4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land - (Includes VA Land Use Task Force)., 1986-1991. (Box 492, Folder 3)
- Index: E7/V4-03. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land - VA Lease., 1976-1991. (Box 492, Folder 4)
- Index: E7/V4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land., 1986-1990. (Box 492, Folder 5)
- Index: E7/V4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land - (Legislation/Deeds/Restrictions)., 1981-1987. (Box 493, Folder 1)
- Index: E7/V4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land - (Request Lease of Jackie Robinson Field)., 1987. (Box 493, Folder 2)
- Index: E7/V4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land., 1971-1984. (Box 493, Folder 3)
- Index: E7/V4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - Veterans Administration Land - VA Lease., 1977-1984. (Box 493, Folder 4)
- Index: E7/W4-01. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - West Campus - West Campus Planning., 1989-1990. (Box 493, Folder 5)
- Index: E7/W4-02. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - West Campus - Interim Staging Facility., 1987-1989. (Box 493, Folder 6)
- Index: E7/W4-01. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - West Campus - West Campus Planning., 1988. (Box 494, Folder 1)
- Index: E7/W4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - West Campus - (Includes Consultant Selection/Recreational Facility/West Campus Planning)., 1984-1988. (Box 494, Folder 2)
- Index: E7/W4. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - West Campus - Science & Technology Building., 1984-1988. (Box 494, Folder 3)
- Index: E7/W4-01. Campus Management - Business Services - Real Estate - West Campus - West Campus Planning., 1979-1987. (Box 494, Folder 4)
- Index: EA31. Campus Management - Finance - Fees - Other Fees - (Includes Grad. Student Research - Mandatory Fee Policy)., 1990-1996. (Box 494, Folder 5)
- Index: EA31. Campus Management - Finance - Fees - Other Fees - (ASUCLA Student Fees)., 1980-1993. (Box 495, Folder 1)
- Index: EA31-01. Campus Management - Finance - Fees - Other Fees - (Special Education Funds)., 1988-1992. (Box 495, Folder 2)
- Index: EA31. Campus Management - Finance - Fees - Other Fees., 1979-1992. (Box 495, Folder 3)
- Index: EA31. Campus Management - Finance - Fees - (Special Education Funds)., 1969-1987. (Box 495, Folder 4)
- Index: EA31. Campus Management - Finance - Fees - Other Fees - (Includes: Fees Usaed for Abortions)., 1970-1980. (Box 495, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1989-1997. (Box 496, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1989-1997. (Box 496, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1978-1996. (Box 496, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1978-1996. (Box 496, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/B-04. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Affirmative Action / Diversity Issues., 1994-1995. (Box 496, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/B-04. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Affirmative Action / Diversity Issues., 1994-1995. (Box 496, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/B-01. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Management Fellowship Program., 1984-1994. (Box 496, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/B-01. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Management Fellowship Program., 1984-1994. (Box 496, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Faculty Career Development & Recruitment Program., 1986-1991. (Box 496, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/B-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Faculty Career Development & Recruitment Program., 1986-1991. (Box 496, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1972-1991. (Box 497, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/B-02. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Status of Hispanics at UC., 1988. (Box 497, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/B-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Faculty Career Development & Recruitment Program., 1981-1986. (Box 497, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Report on Affirmative Action to Regents., 1980-1985. (Box 497, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1984. (Box 497, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Staff Affirmative Action Training & Devt Program., 1978-1984. (Box 498, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Systemwide Affirmative Action Steering Committee., 1981-1984. (Box 498, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1979-1983. (Box 498, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/B-01. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Management Fellowhip Program., 1980-1983. (Box 498, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/B-03. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Faculty Career Development & Recruitment Program., 1978-1981. (Box 498, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Affirmative Action Office Coordinator Committee., 1980-1981. (Box 499, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/B-01. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Management Fellowship Program., 1978-1980. (Box 499, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Annual Report to Legislature., 1976-1979. (Box 499, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide - Universitywide Affirm Action Adv. Cmte Report., 1978. (Box 499, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1975-1978. (Box 499, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1974. (Box 499, Folder 6)
- Index: BB33/B. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Universitywide., 1970-1972. (Box 500, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/D5-01. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Military Recruiting on Campus., 1976-1985. (Box 500, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/D5. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Implementation of the Plan., 1978-1979. (Box 500, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/D5. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Implementation of the Plan., 1976. (Box 500, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/D5. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Implementation of the Plan., 1973. (Box 500, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/D5-01. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Military Recruiting on Campus., 1985-1992. (Box 501, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/D5-02. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Implementation of the Plan - Sexual Orientation., 1976-1991. (Box 501, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/D5. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Implementation of the Plan., 1973-1987. (Box 501, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/D5. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Implementation of the Plan., 1984-1985. (Box 501, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1975-1979. (Box 501, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1975-1979. (Box 502, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1976-1978. (Box 502, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1972-1977. (Box 502, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1972-1976. (Box 502, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1975. (Box 502, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1974 October-1975 July. (Box 502, Folder 6)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1974. (Box 503, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Governmental Relations., 1974 February-August. (Box 503, Folder 2)
- Index: D:0.5. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division of the Academic Senate - General - Golden Years Material from VC Charles Office., 1979. (Box 503, Folder 3)
- Index: DA69/L65. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Cmts Boards & Councils., 1991-1993. (Box 503, Folder 4)
- Index: DE1. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Academic, Planning & Budget - Administration & Staff - Basic Interest Reports., 1981-1984. (Box 503, Folder 5)
- Index: ID7(A-Z). Public Relations - Representation at Inaugurations (Commencements) Out of State Institutions., 1980-1996. (Box 504, Folder 1)
- Index: RF10. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - Chancellors Athletic & Recreation Policies Commission., 1986-1988. (Box 504, Folder 2)
- Index: U1-01. Instruction - Accreditation - Council for Higher Education in Accreditation., 1994-1996. (Box 504, Folder 3)
- Index: U1. Instruction - Accreditation., 1969-1992. (Box 504, Folder 4)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Association of School and Colleges (WASC)., 1971-1995. (Box 504, Folder 5)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - (Survey of Undergraduates)., 1984-1994. (Box 504, Folder 6)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Association of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1989 Accreditation 3 of 3)., 1989-1991. (Box 505, Folder 1)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1989 Accreditation 2 of 3). (Box 505, Folder 2)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1989 Accreditation 1 of 3)., 1988-1989. (Box 505, Folder 3)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1984 Accreditation 3 of 3). (Box 505, Folder 4)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1984 Accreditation 2 of 3). (Box 505, Folder 5)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC)., 1986. (Box 505, Folder 6)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1984 Accreditation 1 of 3)., 1981-1984. (Box 506, Folder 1)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Association of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1978 Accreditation 3 of 3)., 1977-1978. (Box 506, Folder 2)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1978 Accreditation 2 of 3)., 1977-1978. (Box 506, Folder 3)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Association of School and Colleges (WASC) - (1978 Accreditation 1 of 3)., 1977-1978. (Box 506, Folder 4)
- Index: U1/WASC. Instruction - Accreditation - Western Assoication of School and Colleges (WASC) - ( 1973 Accreditation)., 1971-1973. (Box 506, Folder 5)
- Index: U19-01. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - Writing Project., 1982-1996. (Box 507, Folder 1)
- Index: U19-03. Instruction - Remedial Educaiton Courses - Mathematics & Science Projects., 1982-1994. (Box 507, Folder 2)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Educaiton Courses - (Includes California Articulation Number System)., 1984-1993. (Box 507, Folder 3)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Transfer of Remedial Courses)., 1990-1991. (Box 507, Folder 4)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Includes Student Preparation Cites Uni- Wide)., 1983-1988. (Box 507, Folder 5)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Includes UCLA Foreign Lang Institue for Spanish Teachers; Calif. Literature Project/Humanities Prog.)., 1984-1986. (Box 508, Folder 1)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Includes OAIP Budget)., 1983-1985. (Box 508, Folder 2)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses., 1983-1985. (Box 508, Folder 3)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Systemwide Committee on Remediation)., 1983-1984. (Box 508, Folder 4)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Science Project)., 1983-1984. (Box 508, Folder 5)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Core Curriculam)., 1979-1984. (Box 509, Folder 1)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Underprepared Students)., 1981-1983. (Box 509, Folder 2)
- Index: U19-01. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - Writing Project., 1980-1982. (Box 509, Folder 3)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - (Underprepared Students)., 1980-1981. (Box 509, Folder 4)
- Index: U19-01. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses - Writing Project., 1975-1980. (Box 510, Folder 1)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses., 1982-1983. (Box 510, Folder 2)
- Index: U19. Instruction - Remedial Education Courses., 1974-1981. (Folder 3)
- Index: U50-02. Instruction - Graduate Programs, General & Policy - Updated Listing of Proposed ORU's and Degeres., 1995-1997. (Box 510, Folder 4)
- Index: U50-01. Instruction - Graduate Programs, General & Policy - Inventory of Academic Programs., 1993-1995. (Box 510, Folder 5)
- Index: U50. Instruction - Graduate Programs, General & Policy., 1969-1995. (Box 511, Folder 1)
- Index: U50-02. Instruction - Graduate Programs, Genreal & Policy - Updated Listing of Proposed Degrees & ORU's., 1993-1995. (Box 511, Folder 2)
- Index: U50-01. Instruction - Graduate Programs, General & Policy - Inventory of Academic Programs., 1988-1992. (Box 511, Folder 3)
- Index: U50-02. Instruction - Graduate Programs, General & Policy - Updated Listing of Proposed Degrees & ORU's., 1990-1991. (Box 511, Folder 4)
- Index: U50-02. Instruction - Graduate Programs, General and Policy - Updated Listings of Proposed Degrees & ORU's., 1978-1989. (Box 512, Folder 1)
- Index: U50. Instruction - Graduate Programs, General and Policy., 1960-1977. (Box 512, Folder 2)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1995-1997. (Box 512, Folder 3)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees - Master of Public Policy., 1995-1997. (Box 512, Folder 4)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees - (Master of Public Polcy Blue Button Item Proposal to Establish a Program of Studies Leading to (MPP) Degree)., 1995 June 14. (Box 512, Folder 4)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1995-1996. (Box 512, Folder 5)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees - Master of Public Policy Degree., 1995. (Box 513, Folder 1)
- Index: U58-02. Instruction - Degrees - M.A. in Dance Movement/Therapy., 1992-1994. (Box 513, Folder 2)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1990-1994. (Box 513, Folder 3)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees- Undergraduate Major in Neuroscience., 1991-1993. (Folder 4)
- Index: U58-01. Instruction - Degrees - Ph.D in Dance., 1991-1992. (Box 513, Folder 5)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1991. (Box 514, Folder 1)
- Index: U58-01. Instruction - Degrees - Ph.D in Dance., 1998-1991. (Box 514, Folder 2)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1990. (Box 514, Folder 3)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees - Includes MFA in Dance., 1982-1989. (Box 514, Folder 4)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1978-1986. (Box 514, Folder 5)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1980-1983. (Box 515, Folder 1)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1973-1980. (Box 515, Folder 2)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1975-1977. (Box 515, Folder 3)
- Index: U58. Instruction - Degrees., 1958-1973. (Box 515, Folder 4)
- Index: X22/S8. Organized Research & Museums - Centers - Survey Research Center., 1964-1975. (Box 515, Folder 5)
- Index: X33/C6. Organized Research & Museums - Other Organized Research Program - Committee on International & Comparative Studies (Name Change to ISOP)., 1977-1997. (Box 516, Folder 1)